apmg-international.com 2013-11-28

# Privacy Policy | APMG-International

We have a legal duty to protect the privacy of all personal and business data obtained from you while you are using this website. This privacy policy explains what information we may collect from you and the purposes for which it will be used. By using this website you give your agreement to the data practices described in this policy.

This website only collects personal and business data from you with your permission, for example if you register or fill in a form. No personal or business data is collected from you without you knowing about it.

Some web usage and technical information is collected by this website to help us improve our service to you, but this does not contain any personal data.

### Changes to this policy

We may make changes to this privacy policy at any time. Changes will be posted here and are effective immediately. Regularly reviewing this page ensures that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances, if any, we will share it with other parties.

### Information that you provide to us

We collect and process data that you provide for specific purposes. You will be asked to provide information about yourself when you use certain site facilities, in order to complete your request or transaction. This may include personal information such as your name, email addresses, mailing address and telephone number. We use this data to provide you with the information, products or services that you request from us and to communicate with you. We may keep a record of any contacts you have with us. We may use the information that you provide for record keeping, statistical, or research purposes.

We only retain this information where required to do so by law; for the length of time needed to provide the service or information you have requested (including any retention period specified by law or by government policy), or for the length of time that you choose to store information or permit us to contact you if you have registered with our website.

### Website usage information

As well as the information that you provide to us as set out above, we receive and store a range of website usage information whenever you use this website. We use this to:

  * assess the effectiveness of marketing campaigns 
  * develop and deliver services and information that better meet your needs 
  * inform you of events, services and products which we believe to be relevant to you, where you have consented to be contacted for such purposes.

Web usage information is collected by our web server and from other sources including search engines, internet service providers, page tagging techniques including JavaScript, and cookies. We use IP addresses to analyze trends, track users' movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

The Data we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside the European Economic Area ("EEA") and may also be processed by staff (who work for us or for one of our suppliers) operating outside the EEA. By submitting your personal Data, you agree to this transfer, storing and/or processing. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with our Privacy Policy.

### Security

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

### Cookies

Cookies are small files that are often created when you visit a website, and which are stored in the cookie directory of your computer. A cookie often includes an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies do not damage your computer. Each website can send its own cookie to your browser if your browser's preferences allow it, but to protect your privacy your browser only permits a website to access the cookies it has already sent to you, not the cookies sent to you by other sites. You do not have to accept cookies. You can decide if you want to accept cookies by changing the settings on your browser to accept all cookies, reject all cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set.

You can find out about cookies and how to manage them at the [AboutCookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/) website.

You have chosen to accept cookies. To de-activate cookies for features such as Google Analytics you can opt-out of accepting cookies 

#### Third party cookies

This site uses third party cookies. We have listed them below with details about why we use them, and where to find further information about them.

**Cookie** | **Name** | **Purpose** | **More information**  
---|---|---|---  
Google Analytics | _utma  
_utmb  
_utmc  
_utmz  | These cookies are used to collect information about how visitors use our site. We use the information to compile reports and to help us improve the site. The cookies collect information in an anonymous form, including the number of visitors to the site, where visitors have come to the site from and the pages they visited. | [Click here for an overview of privacy at Google](http://www.google.com/intl/en_uk/analytics/privacyoverview.html)  
Video Cloud Player | BC_BANDWIDTH | This cookie is used to collect information regarding bandwidth capability for progressive download deliveries. |   
  
### Links to other websites

This website contains links to other websites. Anonymous visit or session information may be passed to other websites for the web usage information purposes described above. None of this information can be related to an individual user of the website. The operators of other sites may collect information from you, which will be used by them in accordance with their own terms and conditions, and privacy policies.

This privacy policy applies only to our website. We are not responsible for privacy practices within any other websites. You should always be aware of this when you leave this website and we encourage you to read the privacy statement on any other website that you visit.

### Controlling your personal information

Where you have consented to receiving communications from us or are currently receiving material relating to products or services, you may at any time ask us to cease sending you such material by [contacting us](http://www.apmg-international.com/en/contact/contact-apmg-en.aspx).

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties.

APMG-International is a subsidiary of The APM Group Limited. You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to:

APM Group Ltd  
Sword House  
Totteridge Road  
High Wycombe  
Buckinghamshire  
HP13 6DG

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.

* * *
